{
    "subject": "resource/Lotte_Stam-Beese",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1903-01-28",
    "human_readable": "Lotte Stam-Beese was born on January 28, 1903.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9085403680801392,
            "question": "When was Lotte Stam-Beese born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7851215600967407,
            "question": "On which day of the month was Lotte Stam-Beese born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7847564816474915,
            "question": "What significant events happened in the year Lotte Stam-Beese was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7537325024604797,
            "question": "What is Lotte Stam-Beese's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6563062071800232,
            "question": "Who were some notable people born on the same day as Lotte Stam-Beese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5582048892974854,
            "question": "What is Lotte Stam-Beese's birthdate in numerical form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5180713534355164,
            "question": "In what year did Lotte Stam-Beese come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.516638994216919,
            "question": "How old would Lotte Stam-Beese be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48408061265945435,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Lotte Stam-Beese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3999433219432831,
            "question": "Is January 28th a common birthday?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lotte Stam-Beese was born on January 28, 1903.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1567_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Lotte Stam-Beese?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1567_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would Lotte Stam-Beese be today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1567_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Lotte Stam-Beese come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1567_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1567_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Lotte Stam-Beese was indeed born on January 28, 1903."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Lotte Beese was born in Reisicht in Silesia, Germany (now Rokitki in Poland) on 28 January 1903\" and \"Lotte Stam-Beese finally died on November 18, 1988 in Krimpen (The Netherlands)\". This supports the statement that Lotte Stam-Beese was born on January 28, 1903."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}